export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: 'Which of these terms means getting the viewpoint of another medical doctor?',
        options: ['Side Effect', 'Family History', 'Diagnosis', 'Second Opinion'],
        answer: 'Second Opinion'
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which of the following does not aid in identifying breast cancer?',
        options: ['Limit Alcohol Consumption', 'Breast Self-Exam', 'Clinical Breast Exam', 'Mammogram'],
        answer: 'Limit Alcohol Consumption'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which of these is a sign or symptom of ovarian cancer?',
        options: ['Abdominal Bloating', 'Change in Appetite', 'Change in Bowel Habits', 'All of the Above'],
        answer: 'All of the Above'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Which of these is a sign or symptom of pancreatic cancer?',
        options: ['Abdominal Pain', 'Jaundice', 'New Diagnosis of Diabetes', 'All of the Above'],
        answer: 'All of the Above'
    }, 
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Staying in shade during the middle of the day, wearing sunscreen, and avoiding indoor tanning can all prevent what condition?',
        options: ['Breast Cancer', 'Skin Cancer', 'Ovarian Cancer', 'Pancreatic Cancer'],
        answer: 'Skin Cancer'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is an additional bodily reaction to a medication besides its intended purpose?',
        options: ['Side Effect', 'Second Opinion', 'Symptom', 'Oncologist'],
        answer: 'Side Effect'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is the term for a doctor who treats cancer?',
        options: ['Dermatologist', 'Hepatologist', 'Oncologist', 'Pediatrician'],
        answer: 'Oncologist'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is cancer?',
        options: ['A Virus', 'Cells Dividing Out Of Control', 'A Bacterial Infection', 'An Environmental Toxin'],
        answer: 'Cells Dividing Out Of Control'
    }, 
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which of the following means using the body\'s immune system to fight cancer?',
        options: ['Physical Therapy', 'Chemotherapy', 'Immunotherapy', 'Occupational Therapy'],
        answer: 'Immunotherapy'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which of the following are behaviors that can prevent cancer?',
        options: ['Avoid Obesity', 'Stay Physically Active', 'Avoid Tobacco', 'All of the Above'],
        answer: 'All of the Above'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'The only way to diagnose most cancers is to perform what procedure?',
        options: ['Ultrasound', 'Biopsy', 'Palpation', 'Blood Test'],
        answer: 'Biopsy'
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Which of the following may increase your risk of cancer?',
        options: ['Family History of Cancer', 'Current Chronic Health Conditions', 'Environmental Toxins', 'All of the Above'],
        answer: 'All of the Above'
    }, 
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'In the United States, which of these is not one of the most common cancers among men: skin, prostate, lung, oral, or colorectal cancer?',
        options: ['Prostate Cancer', 'Oral Cancer', 'Colorectal Cancer', 'Skin Cancer'],
        answer: 'Oral Cancer'
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'In the United States, which of these is not one of the most common cancers among women: skin, stomach, breast, lung, colorectal, or uterine cancer?',
        options: ['Skin Cancer', 'Stomach Cancer', 'Breast Cancer', 'Lung Cancer'],
        answer: 'Stomach Cancer'
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'What is a cancer screening test?',
        options: ['A Test that Attemps to Detect Cancer Early', 'A Test to See Which Cancer Treatment to Use', 'An Opinion from Another Doctor', 'A Surgical Device'],
        answer: 'A Test that Attemps to Detect Cancer Early'
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Which of these can cause cancer?',
        options: ['Radiation', 'Lead', 'Asbestos', 'All of the Above'],
        answer: 'All of the Above'
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: 'True or false: cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy are more likely to catch a contagious disease.',
        options: ['True', 'False'],
        answer: 'True'
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: 'Bloody stools, changes in bowel movements, and anemia are symptoms of which cancer?',
        options: ['Throat Cancer', 'Thyroid Cancer', 'Skin Cancer', 'Colon Cancer'],
        answer: 'Colon Cancer'
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: 'Which of the following is a recommended screening test for cervical cancer?',
        options: ['Pap Smear', 'Mammogram', 'Colonoscopy', 'All of the Above'],
        answer: 'Pap Smear'
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: 'Which of the following is a recommended test for colon cancer?',
        options: ['Mammogram', 'X-ray', 'Pap Smear', 'Colonoscopy'],
        answer: 'Colonoscopy'
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: 'Which of these germs causes the most health care-associated infections (HAIs)?',
        options: ['Rhinovirus', 'Norovirus', 'Varicella', 'Clostridium Difficile'],
        answer: 'Clostridium Difficile'
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: 'What is a health care-associated infection (HAI)?',
        options: ['A Disease You can Catch from Anyone', 'An Infection from Receiving Health Care', 'Cancer', 'A Food Allergy'],
        answer: 'An Infection from Receiving Health Care'
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: 'Cancer returning after treatment is the definition of what term?',
        options: ['Diagnosis', 'Stage I', 'Recurrence', 'Prognosis'],
        answer: 'Recurrence'
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: 'Which of the following tests new treatments for illnesses on human subjects?',
        options: ['Clinical Trial', 'Recurrence', 'Chemotherapy', 'Prevention'],
        answer: 'Clinical Trial'
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: 'Difficulties with memory and concentration as a result of undergoing chemotherapy describes which symptom?',
        options: ['Pins and Needles', 'Chemo Brain', 'Stroke', 'Tumor'],
        answer: 'Chemo Brain'
    }
]